Like was able to make the videos for free. Um, and they had just a watermark on it right now
It's like, I guess they changed it. They're not doing the videos on it. So I use I mean, there's like different ones like um
google vio and um
Hold on. Hold on. Let me write this down. Yeah
vio
Oh, okay. Yeah, and then I mean, I guess like the slide right up. I don't know. Yeah
Fully, yeah, you're you're to my knowledge and all kinds of stuff, right?
And and then started starting physical violence and then Christine was like,
Well, you know what no Jerry's gonna convict you because you know
You know the look at his videos and see what a lunatic he is and I think it's just it's just a shame the whole thing went to this point
I mean you guys would have you know, oh my god
I mean and I got it yesterday. I said our messes and it's like let's end this now
I think just take down the dog scene videos of my family and then I will
Um, you know or and I said like looking to your heart and and then she's like you don't know
It's in my heart like literally was like that's scary and then um and started yelling like
Someone said oh my god
Honestly, the only thing I can say the best thing would be to just fucking just leave it alone
Are you gonna listen to it with me or no?
Yeah, I get too much. I get too much. I gotta take off. Go ahead. Okay, man. I need to do the banner
No problem. Thank you. No problem.
She made threats on recording this.
Do you understand that I would theoretically be justified to do things that I never would do? Yeah.
So I think he needs to stop immediately.
And those of you who are enabling and contributing don't be surprised.
If certain things come upon you leaving and that's what I'm saying to this asshole
known as Gotti
Trying to sit there straddling the thing that is to I didn't realize that he was a kind of piece of shit that he seems to be
I thought well for and Christine knows this
Consistently keep saying well, what if you didn't do this?
What if you didn't do that? Why can't you cut the cord? And if you can't cut the cord,
don't make it come negative upon me. And if you can't do that, don't be surprised as things
happen to you. I already warned him once.
He doesn't take warnings well, nor does he take leave me alone, which is very succinct to the point.
Hey, uh, it's like, pause it for a second, pause it.
Well, then that means that he needs to be inspected.
Got it.
Who's talking over the track?
Oh, that's, um, that's INX.
She's recording this for me.
Oh, she's recording it, um, but talking to herself and commenting on the track.
Yeah, because, um, because, uh...
I because it's because she deleted the slide right after and so I know I knew she would. Oh, okay
I thought I thought she was talking to you about the trucker. Okay. Yeah, go ahead
to the lies I've said that
Okay, I need me institutionalized and there's a lot of things that needs to be examined
And that's why I consistently name the legal team of Riviera
Center management and Riviera
Properties
Yeah
It's gonna go pretty far figure out what that means. Yeah, I think so. Um, I think so
You and I know Alex, you know a little bit probably more than I think you know about me, but I have four adult sons four
Let me tell you, Christy, I know that certain people have been like, Oh, Alex is bashing
Christine because she says that she would never be over my friend.
What I define as friend, like friend, friend, right?
It's who I know in my.
personal circle, physical life. Yes. Okay. I'm not saying, oh, if I were to ever encounter
Christine in person, I would not be your friend. That's not the case. But what I do know is that
you and I live very different lives. And I know that online is one thing. And I know that
You know, there might be a chance, but I'm not saying that you're, I look up to the kind of person you are. You've raised from what you said, multiple children, you've worked in the healthcare industry successfully.
Yep.
You're, you're to my knowledge in a relationship, I could be wrong, but I think so.
42 years.
Better than what many people, I mean, you're a success story.
Okay, right. Oh, you know what?
My mom's you
that she's trashing, saying she's a bad person
because she raised a horrible son and stuff.
My mom's a mother.
My mom was a volunteer, actually, in hospitals.
And also, she was married for over 42 years, right?
And so, but that's a success for Christine,
but it's like, my mom, she just says horrible things
about her and just trashing her name.
Gosh, she's my whole family, it's just terrible.
Yeah, it's like let me let me say this before I go let me say let me say I'm not taking any size in this
I'm not taking any side. You should got it because
I know I know I'm not saying anything negative about her
As a as a hurt person man, and she feels like she was hurt by you. Okay, well, she's lying
She's lying whatever whatever reason she has. This is what she's doing and she's laughing
All right, so if you if you both if you both continue to hurt each other, it's gonna always gonna
No, no, but but she perceives it she perceives what you're doing
She perceives it as you hurting her
Okay, that's that's all I'm sick. I'm not I'm not taking anybody side. I'm just saying that
All right. All right, bro. Thanks. I'll talk to you
I'm tired of this divide and conquer BS
I'm sick and tired of
Even you use some payback Alex. Let's look at what's going to get AIDS
I have raised four I have raised four sons and I think they are are very good men and I'm going to tell you I had a son
act like psych. Man, I would intervene to the point if I had to go to court and get custodial
woman who is successful and you're a mother and they know damn well they can't pull the
wool over your eyes. That's what it is. Okay? They liked me for a while because I guess they
thought I was Oprah Winfrey. Wrong. Oh no. Okay. We were talking about how to get psyched once
have to happen, is state intervention, because his family, I think he's a black male didn't
extort his family. When I really think about the chain of events, I think about the whole thing,
I think that they're probably scared of him. Oh, I would be scared.
They threw over the curb and he told me to shut up and leave me alone.
This is the first time he's been exposed and I'm not afraid of his family, I'm not afraid of the
And I'm never gonna stop until y'all meet. I'm never gonna stop just so you know
Right. Thank you for letting me on your panel. Oh, of course Alex. I'm gonna probably end the live anyways
You guys get something to eat have a good night. It was fun, you know
Wild in and imagining what we would do is the thing that is on an island
Not that background he has. It needs to be more like tropical that he has. Like where he is, it looks like the end of the world or something like that.
Alex, I'm sorry. Alex, I'm sorry. Excuse me. Psyche, I've told you over and over, you're not allowed to restrain me.
I'll do it maybe in the future, but you definitely not like you're not
Panel right now. I'm saying
leave beta alone
Leave people who don't want to deal with you anymore alone
Create your own content. You I mean you live in a beautiful place. I've seen it first hand
Why it's I mean, that's what I understand
What's the problem?
really
What's
He's like he when I get a little alive. I'm gonna definitely come and report your fucking life not to go on your channel
Leave me the fuck alone. Really? I mean
I'm believable
IRL for the women like beta just just
Older single woman on her e-scooter IRL. I might get hurt, but hey, it's okay. I
Need to get it you eat like a little e-scooter
But what does I mean? Oh my neighbor you fuck off fuck off. It's not hard
Just keep doing your psyche. Keep up something about people.
All right, I'm going to call Alex Christine.
I'm going to make sure I report you though. I'll make sure.
Okay.
Bye, Alex. Thank you for understanding us to you too.
Um, thing that is.
Yes. Thank you, Bita.
Any thoughts? Any thoughts on, uh.
Go eat something. Have another gummy.
Maybe have a drink, drink, and then come back in an hour.
Who knows I mean like let me I don't think I will but honestly
I'm gonna ignore a lot of the bullshit with these people that are gonna just talk about the same old shit
You know how many people are gonna talk about beta beta beta beta beta?
You know you have nothing better to do with your life and I live rent free in your fucking head
Leave me the fuck alone
Eventually you're gonna get the fucking head
Alright, and if you have been like fucking talking like crazy shit about me, don't come back. Alright, really don't come back. I'm just watching.
Restart your channel to restart your panel.
And I would advise you remove the fucking shit about me because I'm definitely reporting it.
Boston! I missed your voice today. Everybody, thank you for hanging in there with me, Maya.
So until we meet on the island, Vita, have a good night.
I'll see you there soon. Make sure you wear your linen.